channels.nl 2017-09-24

# Channels FAQ

The Channels has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Channels. 

**General**

The Channels does not collect any information of our visitors such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. The Channels will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission. 

Knowing that you use certain services or features may help us to offer you better and more relevant content and advertisements. But as with all personally identifiable information, we do not make this available to any third parties without your permission. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. 

**IP address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. Channels is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Third party**

The Channels works with a third party that serves ads to this site. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact webmaster@channels.nl
